<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--

    Copyright (C) 2016 Tirasa

    Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
    you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
    You may obtain a copy of the License at

            http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

    Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
    distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
    WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
    See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
    limitations under the License.

-->
<!DOCTYPE properties SYSTEM "http://java.sun.com/dtd/properties.dtd">
<properties>
  <entry key="aopalliance:aopalliance"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the AOP Alliance (Java/J2EE AOP standards).]]></entry>
  <entry key="com.fasterxml.jackson"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the Jackson project.]]></entry>
  <entry key="com.zaxxer.HikariCP"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the HikariCP project.]]></entry>
  <entry key="com.google.guava:guava"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the Google Guava project.
Copyright (c) 2016 The Guava Authors.]]></entry>
  <entry key="com.sun.xml.bind"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the JAXB project.
Copyright (c) 2013-2016 The JAXB project.]]></entry>
  <entry key="io.dropwizard.metrics"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the Metrics project.
Copyright (c) 2010-2014 Coda Hale, Yammer.com]]></entry>
  <entry key="io.swagger"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the Swagger project.
Copyright 2016 SmartBear Software]]></entry>
  <entry key="javax.annotation:javax.annotation-api"><![CDATA[This product includs software developed by Oracle.
Copyright (c) 2012-2013 Oracle and/or its affiliates. All rights reserved.]]></entry>
  <entry key="javax.validation:validation-api"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the Bean Validation Project (http://beanvalidation.org).
Copyright (c) Red Hat, Inc., Emmanuel Bernard]]></entry>
  <entry key="javax.jws:jsr181-api"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the Java Community Process (https://jcp.org/en/jsr/detail?id=181).
 Copyright (c) 2013 Oracle and/or its affiliates. All rights reserved.]]></entry>
  <entry key="javax.xml.soap:javax.xml.soap-api"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the SAAJ Standard Implementation (https://saaj.java.net/).
 Copyright (c) 2013 Oracle and/or its affiliates. All rights reserved.]]></entry>
  <entry key="javax.ws.rs:javax.ws.rs-api"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the JAX-RS project.
Copyright (c) 2014, Oracle Corporation and/or its affiliates. All rights reserved.]]></entry>
  <entry key="jakarta.ws.rs:jakarta.ws.rs-api"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the Eclipse Project for JAX-RS.
Eclipse Project for JAX-RS is a trademark of the Eclipse Foundation.
All content is the property of the respective authors or their employers. For more information regarding authorship of content, please consult the listed source code repository logs.]]></entry>
  <entry key="javax.xml.ws:jaxws-api"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the JAX-WS project.
 Copyright (c) 1997-2013 Oracle and/or its affiliates. All rights reserved.]]></entry>
  <entry key="joda-time:joda-time"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the Joda Time project.
Copyright (c) 2002-2016 Joda.org. All Rights Reserved.]]></entry>
  <entry key="net.sourceforge.serp:serp"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the SERP Project.
Copyright (c) 2002-2007, A. Abram White http://serp.sourceforge.net/
All rights reserved.]]></entry>
  <entry key="net.tirasa.connid"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the ConnId project.
Copyright 2008-2009 Sun Microsystems, Inc. All rights reserved.
Copyright 2011-2016 Tirasa S.r.l. All rights reserved.]]></entry>
  <entry key="org.activiti"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the Activiti BPM Platform project.]]></entry>
  <entry key="org.aspectj:aspectjweaver"><![CDATA[This product includes AspectJ (>= 1.52) software developed by the Eclipse
Software Foundation.]]></entry>
  <entry key="org.codehaus.woodstox:stax2-api"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the Stax 2 Extension API Project.]]></entry>
  <entry key="org.codehaus.woodstox:woodstox-core-asl"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the Woodstox Project.]]></entry>
  <entry key="org.jasypt:jasypt"><![CDATA[This project includes software developed by the Jasypt project.
Copyright (c) 2014 The JASYPT team. All Rights Reserved]]></entry>
  <entry key="org.javassist:javassist"><![CDATA[This product includes softare developed by the Javassist project.
Copyright (C) 1999- by Shigeru Chiba, All rights reserved.]]></entry>
  <entry key="org.mybatis:mybatis"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the MyBatis project.]]></entry>
  <entry key="org.quartz-scheduler:quartz"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by Terracotta. Inc.
Quartz Scheduler source code and documentation are Copyright (c) Terracotta, Inc.]]></entry>
  <entry key="org.reflections:reflections"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the Reflections project.]]></entry>
  <entry key="org.slf4j"><![CDATA[This products includes software developed by the Simple Logging Facade for Java (SLF4J) project.
Copyright (c) 2004-2016 QOS.ch.]]></entry>
  <entry key="org.springframework"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by SpringSource.
Copyright (c) 2004-2016 SpringSource
All rights reserved.]]></entry>
  <entry key="highlightjs"><![CDATA[This product includes the Javascript syntax highlighter.
Copyright (c) 2006, Ivan Sagalaev]]></entry>
  <entry key="jquery"><![CDATA[This product includes the jQuery Core JavaScript Library.
Copyright 2007, 2016 jQuery Foundation and other contributors.]]></entry>
  <entry key="jquery-ui"><![CDATA[This product includes the jQuery UI JavaScript Library.
Copyright 2007, 2015 jQuery Foundation and other contributors.]]></entry>
  <entry key="org.yaml:snakeyaml"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the SnakeYAML project.]]></entry>
  <entry key="Eonasdan-bootstrap-datetimepicker"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the Bootstrap 3 Datepicker project.
Copyright (c) 2015 Jonathan Peterson (@Eonasdan)]]></entry>
  <entry key="animate.css"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the Animate.css project.
Copyright (c) 2016 Daniel Eden]]></entry>
  <entry key="args4j:args4j"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the args4j project.
Copyright (c) 2013 Kohsuke Kawaguchi and other contributors]]></entry>
  <entry key="bootbox"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the Bootbox.js project.
Copyright (C) 2011-2015 by Nick Payne nick@kurai.co.uk]]></entry>
  <entry key="bootstrap"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the Bootstrap project.
Copyright (c) 2011-2016 Twitter, Inc.]]></entry>
  <entry key="codemirror"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the CodeMirror project.
Copyright (C) 2016 by Marijn Haverbeke <marijnh@gmail.com> and others]]></entry>
  <entry key="codemirror"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the Modernizr project.
Copyright (C) 2016]]></entry>
  <entry key="jsplumb"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the jsPlumb project.
Copyright (c) 2010 - 2014 jsPlumb, http://jsplumbtoolkit.com/]]></entry>
  <entry key="wsdl4j:wsdl4j"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the Web Services Description Language for Java project.
Copyright (c) Dice.
All Rights Reserved.]]></entry>
  <entry key="ionicons"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the Ionicons project.
Copyright (c) 2016 Drifty (http://drifty.com/)]]></entry>
  <entry key="com.googlecode.wicket-jquery-ui"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the Wicket - jQuery UI project.
Copyright 2012-2013 Sebastien Briquet]]></entry>
  <entry key="jquery-cookie"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the jquery.cookie project.
Copyright 2014 Klaus Hartl]]></entry>
  <entry key="jquerypp"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the jQuery++ project.
Copyright (C) 2012 Bitovi]]></entry>
  <entry key="org.webjars.npm:moment"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the Moment.js project.
Copyright (c) 2011-2016 Tim Wood, Iskren Chernev, Moment.js contributors]]></entry>
  <entry key="org.webjars.npm:moment-jdateformatparser"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the moment-jdateformatparser project.
Copyright (c) 2013 MadMG]]></entry>
  <entry key="org.ow2.asm:asm"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the ASM project.
Copyright (c) 2000-2011 INRIA, France Telecom
All rights reserved.]]></entry>
  <entry key="org.threeten:threetenbp"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the ThreeTen Backport project.
Copyright (c) 2007-present, Stephen Colebourne & Michael Nascimento Santos]]></entry>
  <entry key="org.threeten:threetenbp"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the spin.js project.
Copyright (c) 2011-2015 Felix Gnass [fgnass at gmail dot com]]]></entry>
  <entry key="typeahead.js"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the typeahead.js project.
Copyright (c) 2013-2014 Twitter, Inc]]]></entry>
  <entry key="x-editable-bootstrap"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the X-editable project.
Copyright (c) 2012 Vitaliy Potapov]]></entry>
  <entry key="bootstrap-select"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the bootstrap-select project.
Copyright (c) 2013-2015 bootstrap-select]]]></entry>
  <entry key="kendo-ui-core"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the Kendo UI project.
Copyright (c) 2014-2015 Telerik]]]></entry>
  <entry key="lodash"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the lodash project.
Copyright jQuery Foundation and other contributors <https://jquery.org/>]]]></entry>
  <entry key="angular-ui-bootstrap"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the AngularJS UI Bootstrap project.
Copyright (c) 2012-2016 the AngularUI Team, https://github.com/organizations/angular-ui/teams/291112]]]></entry>
  <entry key="angular-ui-router"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the AngularJS UI Router project.
Copyright (c) 2013-2015 The AngularUI Team, Karsten Sperling]]></entry>
  <entry key="angular-ui-select"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the AngularJS UI Select project.
Copyright (c) 2013-2014 AngularUI]]></entry>
  <entry key="org.webjars.bower:angular"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the AngularJS project.
Copyright (c) 2014-2016 Google, Inc. http://angular.io]]></entry>
  <entry key="org.webjars.bower:angular-translate"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the Angular Translate project.
Copyright (c) <2014> <pascal.precht@gmail.com>]]></entry>
  <entry key="org.webjars.bower:bootstrap-fileinput"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the Bootstrap File Input project.
Copyright (c) 2014 - 2016, Kartik Visweswaran Krajee.com All rights reserved.]]></entry>
  <entry key="org.webjars.bower:FileSaver.js"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the FileSaver.js project.
Copyright (c) 2015 Carlos A. Gomes.]]></entry>
  <entry key="org.webjars.bower:select2"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the Select2 project.
Copyright (c) 2012-2015 Kevin Brown, Igor Vaynberg, and Select2 contributors]]></entry>
  <entry key="org.webjars.bower:ng-password-strength"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the ng-password-strength project.
Copyright (c) 2014 Salvador Subarroca subarroca@gmail.com]]></entry>
  <entry key="org.webjars.bower:ng-password-strength"><![CDATA[This product contains unmodified binary redistributions for H2 database engine,
which is dual licensed and available under a modified version of the MPL 1.1 (Mozilla Public License) or under the
(unmodified) EPL 1.0 (Eclipse Public License).
An original copy of the license agreement can be found at: http://www.h2database.com/html/license.html]]></entry>
  <entry key="be.cyberelf.nanoxml:lite"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the NanoXML project.
Copyright (c) 2000-2002 Marc De Scheemaecker, All Rights Reserved.]]></entry>
  <entry key="jline:jline"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the Jline v2 project.
Copyright (c) 2002-2016, the original author or authors.
All rights reserved.]]></entry>
  <entry key="org.hamcrest:hamcrest-core"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the Hamcrest project.
Copyright (c) 2000-2015 www.hamcrest.org
All rights reserved.]]></entry>
  <entry key="org.jdom:jdom2"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the JDOM project.
 Copyright (C) 2000-2012 Jason Hunter & Brett McLaughlin.
 All rights reserved.]]></entry>
  <entry key="org.picocontainer:picocontainer"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the PicoContainer project.
 Copyright (C) 2003-2011 PicoContainer Committers. All rights reserved.]]></entry>
  <entry key="com.github.insubstantial:trident"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the Trident project.
 Copyright (c) 2005-2010 Trident Kirill Grouchnikov. All Rights Reserved.]]></entry>
  <entry key="com.fasterxml.uuid:java-uuid-generator"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the Java Uuid Generator (JUG) project.]]></entry>
  <entry key="jQuery-slimScroll"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the slimScroll project.
Copyright (c) 2011 Piotr Rochala (http://rocha.la)]]></entry>
  <entry key="org.opensaml"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the Shibboleth project.]]></entry>
  <entry key="net.sf.ehcache:ehcache"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by Terracotta. Inc.
Ehcache source code and documentation are Copyright (c) Terracotta, Inc.]]></entry>
  <entry key="org.bouncycastle:bcprov-jdk15on"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the Legion of the Bouncy Castle.
Copyright (c) 2000-2016 The Legion of the Bouncy Castle Inc. (http://www.bouncycastle.org)]]></entry>
  <entry key="google-diff-match-patch"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the google-diff-match-patch project.
Copyright (c) 2006 Google Inc.]]></entry>
  <entry key="org.webjars.bower:chart.js"><![CDATA[This product includes software developed by the Chart.js project.
Copyright (c) 2018 Chart.js Contributors]]></entry>
</properties>
